merabheja.com 2019-06-05

# Disclaimer & Privacy Policy

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://merabheja.com/contact/).

we consider the privacy of our visitors to be extremely important. This privacy policy document describes in detail the types of personal information is collected and recorded by merabheja.com and how we use it.

 **Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, merabheja.com makes use of log files. These files merely logs visitors to the site – usually a standard procedure for hosting companies and a part of hosting services’s analytics. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
merabheja.com does not use cookies.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

→ Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on merabheja.com.  
→ Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our site’s visitors based upon their visit to merabheja.com and other sites on the Internet.  
→ Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

**Our Advertising Partners**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include …….

  * Google

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology in their respective advertisements and links that appear on merabheja.com and which are sent directly to your browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by our site’s third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on the site.

merabheja.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

 **Third Party Privacy Policies**

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. https://merabheja.com/’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Consent**  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our privacy policy and agree to its terms.

## Terms of Use

All content provided on this merabheja.com blog is for informational purposes only. The owner of this blog makes no representations as to the accuracy or completeness of any information on this site or found by following any link on this site.

The owner of merabheja.com will not be liable for any errors or omissions in this information nor for the availability of this information. The owner will not be liable for any losses, injuries, or damages from the display or use of this information.
